Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Blue Vibes, 1997 October 26 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0108)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: "Blue Vibes Xtra"
  - Cameron Corner, 1997 December 03 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0112)
    Cable13 tape number: #11
  - Duke vs UVA, 1997 December 06 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0113)
    Cable13 tape number: 2nd half; Other notes: at CIS
  - Duke vs UVA, 1997 December 06 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0114)
    Cable13 tape number: 1st half; Other notes: at CIS
  - Film & Video program: Screening Room, 1997 December 07 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0947)
    Other notes: Jack Parrish
  - Duke at Michigan, 1997 December 13 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0115)
  - Suplex Dreams: A Wrestling Mockumentary, 1998 August (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0151)
    Program Length: 40mins; Other notes: Prod: Jesse Eisenhardt
  - DUI: First Semester Ever, 1998 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0156)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Prod: Porter Mason, Sean Loughlin
  - DUI: First Semester Ever, 1998 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0157)
    Program Length: 61mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Prod: Porter Mason, Sean Loughlin
  - Lorca's B-Day, 1998 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0158)
  - Bob Woodward, 1998 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0159)
  - Diwali: Final, 1998 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0160)
  - Diwali: Final, 1998 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0161)
  - "Door #3" by Nic de Armendi, 1998 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0162)
  - Blue Vibes - Unmarked Pavement, 1998 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0163)
  - Live with Jeri Powell (DSG Pres), 1998 (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0164)
    Other notes: Training Show
  - Diwali, 1998 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0165)
  - Kammerer Award Compilation Master, 1998 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0166)
    Other notes: Peter Coyle
  - Video Yearbook, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0167)
    Other notes: Master
  - Cameron Corner '98 '99 Episode #2, 1998-1999 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0168)
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, 1998 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0034)
  - Duke Video Yearbook: The Eye of the Devil, 1998 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0035)
    Other notes: Prod: Katherine J. Brennan, Michelle Brown, Sean Loughlin
  - Duke vs Clemson, 1998 January 17 (Box 100, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0128)
  - Duke vs UVA, 1998 January 24 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0129)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: at UVA
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1998 February 02 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0130)
    Cable13 tape number: S3/E1; Other notes: Joe Casola & Elise Hartley
  - Duke vs NC State, 1998 February 08 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0131)
  - Joe College, 1998 February 09 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0132)
  - Joe College, 1998 February 09 (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0133)
    Program Length: 29mins4secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 1; Other notes: Broadcast Master
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs Florida St., 1998 February 10 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0134)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: 0
  - Imam w/ Dean Mohammed, 1998 February 11 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Hi8-0002)
    Other notes: Taped at Griffith Film Theatre, presented by DUU Major speakers
  - Spencer Robertson's Playground, 1998 February 16 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0135)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep 1
  - At Clemson, 1998 February 19 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0136)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Field work, interview with kids working, cutaways in BIM
  - The Basement of Blue Vibes, 1998 March 01 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0137)
    Other notes: Prod: Justin Alston & Jason Jordan
  - Black Period, 1998 March 01 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0138)
    Other notes: BV Productions, Prod: Justin Alston & Jason Jordan
  - Spencer Robertson's Neighborhood, 1998 March 02 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0139)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Prod: Benjy Zazove, Robert Gehring
  - Orpheus Descending, 1998 March 02 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0140)
    Program Length: 50mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Dir: Jody McAuliffe, Crew: Benjamin Epps
  - Orpheus Descending, 1998 March 02 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0141)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Dir: Jody McAuliffe, Crew: Benjamin Epps
  - Joe College 2, 1998 March 09 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0142)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Joe College 2, 1998 March 09 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0143)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1998 March 10 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0144)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #5; Other notes: Live NCAA Tourney Preview Show
  - Black Period (Blue Vibes), 1998 April 05 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0145)
  - Blue Vibes - The Basement, 1998 April 12 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0146)
    Cable13 tape number: Show #2
  - Black Period (Blue Vibes), 1998 April 12 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0147)
  - Blue Vibes - "Chillin", 1998 April 19 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0148)
  - Blue Vibes, 1998 April 24 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0149)
  - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1998 May 17 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0057)
    Other notes: Wallace Wade Stadium
  - The Epps Files, 1998 July 03 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0150)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Crew: Jeff Dillinger, Benjamin Epps, Rob Gehring, Lisa Anderson, Liz Bell, Sean Loughlin, Milly Sanders, Adam Saunders, Chris Schuessler
  - Fuqua-ILE, 1998 August 24 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0152)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #2; Other notes: Library Geneen
  - Duke vs. JMU-Soccer, 1998 September 12 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Hi8-0003)
    Other notes: Duke 1-0
  - Duke vs. Red Wings, 1998 September 25 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Hi8-0004)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #2; Other notes: 5.16-Tommy Parrott, Post Game Interviews
  - Step Show, 1998 September 26 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Hi8-0005)
  - Blue Vibes - The Velvet Rope Experience, 1998 November 01 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0153)
  - Blue Vibes - Urban Element, 1998 November 01 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0154)
  - Cameron Corner, 1998 November 14 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0155)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: #1; Other notes: Season Premier, Shane Battier
  - Kenan K. Holley: Inferno Productions, 1999 April (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0171)
  - DUI's Christmas Show "Jesus' 21st Birthday", 1999 December (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0174)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Filmed by Bret Runestad
  - Telethon, 1999 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0177)
    Cable13 tape number: Hour #1
  - DUI's Big Show 2, 1999 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0178)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Crew: Nathan Samras, Porter Mason
  - DUI's Big Show 2, 1999 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0179)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Crew: Nathan Samras
  - Telethon '99 Hour #5, 1999 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0180)
  - Devilosity Video Yearbook, 1999 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0036)
    Other notes: Duke University Union
  - Kammerer Submissions, 1999 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0037)
  - Devilosity: Video Yearbook, 1999 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0038)
    Other notes: Prod: Michelle Brown
  - Carolina at Duke, 1999 January 27 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0169)
    Cable13 tape number: 2nd half
  - Speak, 1999 February 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0949)
    Cable13 tape number: 3 of 5
  - Speak, 1999 February 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0950)
    Cable13 tape number: 4 of 5
  - Blue Vibes - Urban Element, 1999 February 21 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0170)
    Other notes: Prod: Justin Alston
  - Pee Yourself, 1999 April 21 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0172)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep 2
  - The Duke Report, 1999 November 22 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0173)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: S1/E1; Other notes: w/ Bill Hatfield
  - Helen, 1999 December 02 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0175)
    Program Length: 65mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Helen, 1999 December 02 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0176)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Cable 13 Promos, 199? April 2 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0181)
    Cable13 tape number: C13
  - Life at Duke, 2000 February (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0183)
    Program Length: 36mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - Keir, 2000 April (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0189)
    Program Length: 49mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - Tip TV, 2000 July (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0192)
    Cable13 tape number: T1/E3; Other notes: Prod: Nic de Armendi
  - DUI's Big Show 3, 2000 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0196)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Crew: Porter Mason, Ben Epps
  - DUI's Big Show 3, 2000 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0197)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Crew: Porter Mason, Ben Epps
  - DUI Big Show #3, 2000 (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0198)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Edited by Porter Mason, Filmed by Ben Epps
  - Grad 2000 Kristine #2 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0199)
  - Blue & White 2000 1st Half (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0200)
  - Cameron Corner 2000-2001 Season Ep 1 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0201)
  - The Duke Report, 2000 January 31 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0182)
    Program Length: 25mins41secs; Cable13 tape number: S1/E2; Other notes: w/ Bill Hatfield, Kimberly Holmes
  - ASA Lunar New Year, 2000 February 19 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0184)
  - ASA Lunar New Year, 2000 February 19 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0185)
  - The Crucible, 2000 March 02 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0186)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape #1
  - The Crucible, 2000 March 02 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0187)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape #2
  - The Crucible, 2000 March 02 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0188)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape #3
  - Tip TV, 2000 June 18 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0190)
    Cable13 tape number: T1/E1; Other notes: Prod: Nic de Armendi
  - Tip TV, 2000 June 25 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0191)
    Program Length: 27mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: T1/E2; Other notes: Prod: Nic de Armendi
  - 2000 Fall Symposium, 2000 September 16 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0193)
    Other notes: Raw Footage, Crew: Rome Hartman, Jay Bilas, Jennifer Zeidman, Bloch
  - The Duke Report, 2000 October 21 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0194)
    Program Length: 33mins51secs; Cable13 tape number: S2/E1; Other notes: 2000 Election Special, Hosts: Bill Hatfield, Kimberly Holmes, 8.8
  - D.O.A. Final Cut, 2000 December 02 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0195)
  - Hoof n' Horn: Grand Hotel, 2001 October (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0210)
    Program Length: 62mins23secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Hoof n' Horn: Grand Hotel, 2001 October (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0211)
    Program Length: 54mins19secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2
  - Fall 2001 Telethon Cameron Corner (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0212)
  - Fall 2001 Telethon DUI Hour 1 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0213)
  - Cameron Corner, 2001 February 19 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0202)
    Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: Mike Dunleavy
  - "Chapter Two" by Neil Simon, 2001 March 30 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0203)
    Cable13 tape number: Act 1; Other notes: Wendell Theatre Group
  - "Chapter Two" by Neil Simon, 2001 March 30 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0204)
    Cable13 tape number: Act 2; Other notes: Wendell Theatre Group
  - Duke Players: The Changeling - Act I, 2001 April 05 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0205)
    Program Length: 80mins22secs
  - Duke Players: The Changeling - Act II, 2001 April 05 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0206)
    Program Length: 70mins
  - The Duke Report, 2001 April 20 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0207)
    Program Length: 47mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E2; Other notes: w/ Bill Hatfield, Kimberly Holmes, Guest: Prof. Michael Munger
  - "Door #3" by Nic de Armendi, 2001 April 28 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0208)
    Program Length: 11mins; Other notes: Short Film
  - A Night with Hoof n' Horn, 2001 May 03 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0209)
    Program Length: 29mins15secs
  - Public Policy 118 Semester Projects, 2002 April (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0217)
    Program Length: 23mins25secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2; Other notes: 1.Eating Disorders at Duke, 2. Campus Safety, 3. Social Life at Duke
  - IDC 2002 Telethon: Iron Duke Chef, 2002 Fall (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0231)
  - Cameron Corner, 2002 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0232)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2; Other notes: Season Wrap-up
  - Alice in Wonderland, 2002 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0233)
    Program Length: 50mins
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0234)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 2; Other notes: Sean Young
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0235)
    Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: Temeka Williams
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0236)
    Other notes: Namita Hoppa, Phillip Kuriam, Alex Lee
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0237)
    Cable13 tape number: #4; Other notes: Sabina Ahmad-Khan
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0238)
    Other notes: Alex, Jin
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0239)
    Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: Sean Young
  - Cameron Corner Promo - Cheerleaders, 2002 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0240)
    Program Length: 23mins41secs
  - ASA '02, 2002 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0241)
    Other notes: Patty
  - Spring 2002 Telethon (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0242)
    Cable13 tape number: 1am & on
  - Open House Reel Sept 2002 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0243)
  - Spring 2K2 Telethon Cameron Corner, 2002 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0244)
  - Spring 2K2 Telethon Dave/Kimmie, 2002 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0245)
  - Hoof n' Horn: Godspell, 2002 January 26 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0214)
    Program Length: 61mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Hoof n' Horn: Godspell, 2002 January 26 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0215)
    Program Length: 44mins36secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2
  - Duke UNC 3-3-02, 2002 March 03 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0216)
  - Hoof n' Horn: Kiss Me, Kate, 2002 April 19 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0218)
    Program Length: 68mins23secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Hoof n' Horn: Kiss Me, Kate, 2002 April 19 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0219)
    Program Length: 52mins48secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2
  - The Duke Report, 2002 April 26 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0220)
    Program Length: 35mins59secs; Cable13 tape number: S3/E2; Other notes: Interview w/ Susan Tifft, w/ Bill Hatfield, Kimberly Holmes
  - Craft Center Dedication, 2002 September 05 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0058)
  - Battier Leadership Tally, 2002 September 12 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0010)
    Other notes: D. Lang
  - Cameron Corner w/ Dahntay Jones, 2002 October 23 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0221)
    Other notes: Raw footage, 8.12
  - Blue-White Game, 2002 October 26 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0222)
    Program Length: 2hrs29mins48secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Pre-game Alumni Game
  - Devil Time, 2002 October 29 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0223)
    Program Length: 1hr23mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep 1; Other notes: Master
  - Cameron Corner, 2002 October 30 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0224)
    Program Length: 32mins57secs; Cable13 tape number: S14/E1; Other notes: w/ Dahntay Jones, Prod: Mike Marion
  - Crossing the Bridge, 2002 October 30 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0225)
    Program Length: 13mins45secs; Other notes: An in depth look at Asian American students
  - Devil Time, 2002 November 05 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0226)
    Program Length: 28min30secs; Cable13 tape number: S1/E2
  - The Duke Report: Credits Packages, 2002 November 09 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0227)
    Other notes: Intro-2:29:29-02:53:12, Close-03:00:00-03:20:29
  - Duke Report Promos, 2002 November 09 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0228)
  - Inside Joke - Hideaway, 2002 November 15 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0009)
    Other notes: "Charlie and the Pirate Factory"
  - Duke vs Army, 2002 November 23 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0229)
  - Duke vs Army, 2002 November 23 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0230)
  - 2003 Telethon (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0253)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2?
  - Spring 2K3 Then DT, 2003 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0254)
  - Telethon, 2003 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0255)
    Cable13 tape number: 1st tape
  - LLL, 2003 Fall (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0001)
  - Clemson at Duke, 2003 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0001)
  - Inside Joke, 2003 April (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0006)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 1
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs Florida St., 2003 January 26 (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0246)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs Florida St., 2003 January 26 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0247)
  - The Duke Report, 2003 February 07 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0248)
    Program Length: 42mins; Other notes: Guests: Bruce Jentleson, Joseph Grieco
  - Small Programs: Pitchforks & DUI, 2003 March 01 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0011)
  - Devil Time: Election Special, 2003 March 04 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0249)
    Program Length: 39mins33secs; Cable13 tape number: 2 (3); Other notes: Master
  - "The Chosen One", 2003 March 31 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0012)
    Program Length: 27mins45secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 7; Other notes: "Henry the 8th I Am"
  - Totally Panuccio, 2003 May 01 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0250)
  - Totally Panuccio, 2003 May 01 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0251)
  - Team Duke 4 FG, 2003 October 11 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0007)
    Cable13 tape number: EZ
  - Blue White Game, 2003 October 25 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0252)
    Program Length: 75mins
  - Duke Women's vs Maryland, 2004 January 22 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0257)
  - Duke Women's Basketball vs Virginia 2-19-04, 2004 February 19 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0256)
  - DSG Meeting - Press Conference, 2004 March 17 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0008)
    Other notes: 1st Final Cut
  - DCS, 2004 September 25 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0015)
    Program Length: 1hr36mins; Other notes: Quitter John, Dillo
  - Dillo, Daniel & Kody, 2004 October 02 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0014)
  - BOTB, 2004 November 19 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0013)
    Other notes: Quitter John, Suspended Principles, And the winner is..‚¬Â¦
  - Dillo, Alex Cornell, Uncle Jemima, 2005 January 29 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0016)
  - Locker Room Interviews (MBB), 2007-2008 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0009)
  - Live High Five, 2008 September 26 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0010)
  - Live High Five & Future Kings of Nowhere, 2008 September 26 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0011)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Ep 1. CCS
  - Studio Survey, 2008 September 27 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0012)
  - Cobalt & The Hired Guns Interview, 2009 March 29 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0002)
  - Last Duke Weekly, 20?? April 17 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0003)
  - Last Duke Weekly, 20?? April 17 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0004)
  - Pippin, January 23 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0002)
  - Pippin, January 23 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0003)
  - Braddigan Interview, February 24 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0004)
    Other notes: Vanessa Vincent
  - Raleigh Cut-Through B-Roll, March 3 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0258)
    Cable13 tape number: EC/SV
  - Dillo Bands - The Members, March 20 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-DVcam-0008)
  - WCBS Air: Sunday, April 26 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0259)
    Program Length: 1hr30mins
  - Kammerer Prize Videos, April 28 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0044)
  - Team 1 & 2 SL, October 2 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-MDV-0005)
  - Blue-White Game, undated (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0260)
    Program Length: 1hr22mins54secs
  - Michigan at Duke, undated (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0261)
  - Michael Dyson Speech and Q&A, undated (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0262)
  - Kevin Nealon Interview, undated (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0263)
    Other notes: Hi-8 Transfer, PACESathideway (girl & Jackie)
  - Safe Ride, undated (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0264)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Prod: John Tingue, Andrew Kapp
  - Aural Pleasures, undated (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0265)
    Program Length: 30mins; Other notes: Prod: Rob Gehring, Nathan Samros
  - "Easy Reading", undated (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0266)
    Program Length: 16mins30secs; Other notes: Crew: Adam Saunders, Benjamin Epps
  - Sportsline, undated (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0267)
    Program Length: 30mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: #13; Other notes: for Telethon
  - Cameron Corner, undated (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0268)
    Program Length: 12mins43secs; Cable13 tape number: #4; Other notes: Highlights: SC State, Michigan, Host: Steven Ross
  - Cameron Corner, undated (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0269)
    Cable13 tape number: S 1; Other notes: Roundtable Segment
  - Show One: An Attempt at Entertainment, undated (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0270)
  - DUI's Big Show 5, undated (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0271)
  - Cyrus X, undated (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0272)
    Program Length: 34mins; Cable13 tape number: #7; Other notes: top 5 pick
  - Hog Farm, undated (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0273)